# Roberto Gauna

## **Software Engineer**

Provo, UT 385-2549282

rgauna@gmail.com

#### Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/rgauna

#### **Github**

github.com/rgauna

#### **Portfolio**

http://rgauna79.github.io/portfoliorjg

#### **Profile**

Full-stack software development with experience in design, installation, testing and maintenance of software systems. Experience in the most cutting-edge development tools and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage independent projects. Good collaboration skills within a productive team.

Education	Skills
(March 2011 – July 2015) UPTP "JJ.  Montilla"  - Bachelor of Engineering - BEng Computer Science in Acarigua - Venezuela	<ul> <li>HTML5, CSS</li> <li>JavaScript (React)</li> <li>Python, (Django)</li> <li>SQL (MySQL, Postgres)</li> <li>Git - Github</li> <li>PHP (Laravel)</li> </ul>

# **Experience**

#### (November 2021 - Present) Innovative Labs - Preweigh Lead

Department Lead.

#### (January 2020 - Present) Innovative Labs - Batching technician

- Pre-weighting products
- Batching.

#### (October 2017 - November 2019) Liberty Press - Binder operator

- Responsible of auto-feeder equipment preparation
- Configure and prepare paper trimmer

### (August 2008 - 2017) G&B Sistemas C.A, Customer service and technical service

- OS Technical service
- Software and hardware issues.

#### (July 2011 - July 2015) Hospital Agua Blanca, Software Developer

- Software Developer
- HTML, PHP, Ajax
- Apache Server, MySQL

## Courses

- freeCodeCamp certifications (online) 2023:
  - Responsive web design.
  - JavaScript Algorithms and data structures.
  - Front-end development libraries.
  - Data visualization
- Odin Project (online) 2023:
  - Full-stack JavaScript Course.